[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Over any given 400-year cycle the 13th day of the month occurs 4800 times. The 13th most often falls on this day of the week.", "correct_answer": "Friday", "incorrect_answers": ["Sunday", "Monday", "Wednesday"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This dog, which was once used as a personal defense dog, police dog and war dog, is often mistakenly believed to be very aggressive.", "correct_answer": "Doberman Pinscher", "incorrect_answers": ["Field Spaniel", "Elo", "Finnish Spitz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who won the first chess tournament in the USA?", "correct_answer": "Paul Morphy", "incorrect_answers": ["Adolph Anderssen", "John Marshall", "Henry  Bird"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first scheduled TV  broadcasts, which began in 1928, originated in which US state?", "correct_answer": "New Jersey", "incorrect_answers": ["California", "New York", "Massachusetts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following do orca NOT do with their food?", "correct_answer": "Regurgitate it for their young", "incorrect_answers": ["Throw it", "Use it as a teaching tool for young orca", "Slam it on the surface of the water"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why was Battery D, Harry Truman\u2019s unit in World War I, so devoted to their Captain Harry?", "correct_answer": "All of these.", "incorrect_answers": ["None of the men died because of a battle.", "Truman always kept his mens safety as primary goal.", "Truman never asked them to do anything he wont do."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is NOT an Oklahoma city?", "correct_answer": "Toledo", "incorrect_answers": ["Peoria", "Burbank", "St. Louis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tyrannosaurus Rex means Tyrant Lizard King.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress was considered for the part of Viola, eventually portrayed by Gwyneth Paltrow, in the 1998 movie Shakespeare in Love?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Meg Ryan", "Kate Winslet", "Winona Ryder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular character did Sally Field portray in the first movie that brought her an Academy Award for Best Actress?", "correct_answer": "Norma Rae", "incorrect_answers": ["Jane Eyre", "Erin Brockovich", "Mary Jane Kelly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This plant with small blue flower heads, often regarded as a weed in the past, is the national flower of Estonia.", "correct_answer": "Blue cornflower", "incorrect_answers": ["Daisy", "Lily", "Dahlia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On which part of the body is the surgical procedure osteotomy performed?", "correct_answer": "Bones", "incorrect_answers": ["Duodenum", "Tonsils", "Smooth muscle tissue"]}]